<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MartinWongReader</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_read">Read</string>
    <string name="title_liked">Liked</string>
    <string name="Account">Account</string>
    <string name="Pokemon">Pokemon</string>
    <string name="Fight">Fight</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">ProfileActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "What I have accomplished.
        I was able to get this intent to show this page as you can tell by clicking on the information button. This intent was an explicit intent as it launched a new activity in my app. This page is meant for me to provide more information on my application.
            Home page: I was able to easily set up the home page by adding two text view and a background image to the page.
            Pokemon Screen: In this screen I was only able to hard code the pokemon as I was on a time limit. If I had more knowledge with Java and Api in java I was going to allow the user to search for his or her pokemon to use for the next screen. On this screen I hard encoded four buttons that have four random move for Rayquaza. (E.S stands for extreme speed) At the moment the search bar and search button are aesthetic.
            Pokemon Fight screen: In this screen I was able to change the image when the attack button was clicked on. I used mathrandom as to set a probability for your pokemon to miss or attakc. If your pokemon missed then Gengar would attack. I was able to set the two to simultaneously attack each other by making if statements. If the numbers were less than 0.5 the pokemon attacked. If not they missed. I wanted to display the four moves for Rayquaza but again I was on a time constraint. I was able to reset the score and game when the user hp was equal to zero or the gengar hp was equal to zero.
            Information: This screen is heavily lacking functionality as it only incorporates a button that launched this page.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
